卡洛琳消失的时候
And at the time of Carolyn's disappearance,
你会如何形容你们那时的婚姻状态
how would you describe the state of your marriage?
我们正深深地相爱着
We were deeply in love.
你能解释一下  为什么卡洛琳死了七年
Can you explain why, seven years after Carolyn's death,
「所谓谋杀」这样的片子
a show like Call It Murder
会选择将你刻画成一个杀手呢
would choose to portray you as a killer?
我声名狼藉
I'm notorious.
像白人版辛普森
The white O.J.
不管发生了什么  人们永远相信最糟的
And no matter what happens, people will believe the worst.
这会是个精彩的故事
It's a good story.
我是无罪释放的
I, uh, was acquitted.
我在一场过失致死的诉讼中获得了胜诉
I prevailed in a wrongful death suit.
谋杀卡洛琳的凶手在牢里
There's someone now in prison for Carolyn's murder.